José Martín Govea López

Front End Developer

in www.linkedin.com/in/magovz k https://profound-croquembouche-eb781f.netlify.app/

PROFILE

I am an IT engineer focused on Front End development with 5+ years of experience working with technologies like HTML, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap, TailWind CSS, JavaScript, React, Angular. I really enjoy what I do and I am looking for a job opportunity where I can contribute with my knowledge and grow personally and professionally.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Developer 04/2020 - 12/2022 Vive Metria Ciudad Victoria, • Design and development of web pages. Tamaulipas, México

• Development and maintenance of web applications.

· Obtaining requirements.

Software Developer 06/2018 - 09/2019 HTA Ciudad Victoria, • Creation and development of designs (Front End). Tamaulipas, México

• Development and maintenance of web applications.

Software Developer 09/2017 - 06/2018 DMAC. Ciudad Victoria, Tamaulipas, México

Design and development of user interfaces for web applications.

• Design and development of web pages.

Software Developer 11/2015 - 12/2015 Budget Planning Department of Tamaulipas (professional practices) Ciudad Victoria, • Design and development of user interfaces for web and desktop applications. Tamaulipas, México

SKILLS

- Knowledge of HTML, CSS, SASS, JavaScript, ¡Query, NodeJS.
- Experience with frameworks and development libraries (Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, React, Angular, Laravel, Django).
- PHP, Python.
- SQL.

PORTFOLIO

https://profound-croquembouche-eb781f.netlify.app/

LANGUAGES

Spanish **English** Native Intermediate

EDUCATION

Information Technology Engineer Universidad Politécnica de Victoria

09/2014 - 12/2017 Ciudad Victoria, Tamaulipas, México